{
    "subject": "resource/Alfred_Peet",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Netherlands",
    "human_readable": "Alfred Peet was born in the Netherlands.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8943310379981995,
            "question": "Where was Alfred Peet born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7894043326377869,
            "question": "When was Alfred Peet born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7410181760787964,
            "question": "What is the name of the city where Alfred Peet was born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5853050947189331,
            "question": "What country is Alfred Peet from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44064489006996155,
            "question": "Did Alfred Peet travel to other countries?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.33677762746810913,
            "question": "Was Alfred Peet a famous entrepreneur?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2805942893028259,
            "question": "Is Alfred Peet still alive today?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20075125992298126,
            "question": "What type of business did Alfred Peet start?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.13640283048152924,
            "question": "Is Alfred Peet known for starting a coffee company?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.11996966600418091,
            "question": "Why is Alfred Peet considered important in the coffee industry?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Alfred Peet was born in the Netherlands.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3475_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Alfred Peet known for starting a coffee company?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3475_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of business did Alfred Peet start?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3475_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Alfred Peet still alive today?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3475_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3475_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3475_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3475_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3475_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3475_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3475_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3475_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3475_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3475_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3475_81.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because all four documents mention that Alfred Peet was indeed born in the Netherlands."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents clearly state that Alfred Peet was born in Alkmaar, Noord-Holland, Netherlands, which supports the statement that Alfred Peet was born in the Netherlands."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}